Class: Assassin<br>Specialization: Coven Mistress<br><br><body_bright>Shadow Witches, Shadow Matriarchs and Shadow Mistresses have a chance to make a free additional shot at the hero's current target. Furthermore every day, new Shadow Witches will join the heroes army depending on the hero level (provided that some of these creatures are present).<br><color_default>Number(Level) : 1(7) 2(19) 3(32) 4(44)
