Class: Necromancer<br>Specialization: Soul Harvester<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each week additional Ghosts, Spectres or Poltergeists will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.45*hero level. No extra creatures will be available before level 2.<br><color_default>The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.