Class: Reaver<br>Specialization: Souldrinker<br><br><body_bright>The Weakness spell does not only lower creature's damage, but also reduces creature's Defense by -1 for every three levels of the hero, starting on first level. Defense of the target(s) is reduced by Level/3, rounded up.<br><color_default>The Defense decrease lasts for the duration of the spell, and is not cumulative. The effect is lost if the spell is replaced by another Curse effect. (Archliches' Curse spell or Spectral Dragons' Cursing Attack ability).