Class: Death Knight<br>Specialization: Dark Rider<br><br><body_bright>All mage guilds in owned Necropolis towns will summon Black Knights instead of Mummies and the hero will already have 5 Dragonblood Crystals available at the start of the game for the purpose of summoning them.<br><color_default>This specialization only works if the hero is present on the map on day one and doesn't work if the hero is hired from the tavern.