Class: Death Knight<br>Specialization: Zombie Lord<br><br><body_bright>All Zombies, Plague Zombies and Rot Zombies in the hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defence for every two levels of the hero, starting on first level. Also at the start of each week more zombies will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.6*hero level.<br><color_default>The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.