Class: Demon Lord<br>Specialization: Hound master<br><br><body_bright>All Hell Hounds, Cerberi and Firehounds in hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defence for every two levels of the hero.<br>Additionally, new Hell Hounds will join the hero's army every day depending on his level (provided that some of these creatures are present).<br><color_default>Number(Level) : 1(2) 2(5) 3(8) 4(11) 5(14) ... 17(50)