Class: Flamekeeper<br>Specialization: Spellwringer<br><br><body_bright>If an enemy hero casts any spell, it can be blocked in his or her spellbook making it impossible to cast that spell again in this combat. The probability of blocking increases with hero level.<br><color_default>When both heroes have the same Level, it leads to a 50%, 33%, 25%, 20% and 16% chance to block spells of level 1 to 5.