Class: Overlord<br>Specialization: Beastmaster<br><br><body_bright>The Lizard Bite ability deals more damage, depending on hero level.<br>Each time of a Rider in hero's army turn comes in combat, there is a chance to boost the ATB of allied Hydras. Chance is 20% + 2% per hero level.<br>Additionally, new Riders join the hero's army every day depending on his level (provided that some of these creatures are present).<br><color_default>Number(Level) : 1(4) 2(10) 3(17) 4(24) 5(30) ... 8(50)