Class: Wizard<br>Specialization: Spell Twister<br><br><body_bright>The hero's Spellpower increases by +1 for every 8 experience levels and the Magic Mirror perk is more effective. There is a higher chance that redirected enemy spells land on one of the enemy units instead of going in a random direction. The improved odds are 40%+hero level*1%.<br><color_default>The trigger chance of Magic Mirror itself is not affected.