Class: Paladin<br>Specialization: Demagogue<br><br><body_bright>Neutral creatures are more likely to join this hero. The hero has a +10% per level bonus to his Army Power evaluation for diplomatic calculations.<br>At the start of each week, every Archer, Footmen, Cleric groups and their upgrades in hero's army are increased by 1% per level. Moreover victories provide this hero with gold and resources.