Class: Shaman<br>Specialization: Daughter of Nature<br><br><body_bright>Every time a friendly stack dies, a group of elementals enters combat at hero's side. Number of elementals increases depending on hero level. In addition, Summon Elementals and Summon Phoenix spells casted by the hero are more powerfull.<br><br><color=blue>Shaman<color=white><br><body_bright>The Hero starts with Sorcery and Refined Mana.