Class: Shaman<br>Specialization: Daughter of Light<br><br><body_bright>The hero starts with Light Magic and Father Sky grants the shaman new light magic and adventure spells spontaneously after levelups. Higher level spells can only be learned if the Hall of Trial/Walker's Hut is upgraded.<br><color_default>The ability to gain new spells follows randomly different patterns but is not based on chance (by lvl 30 you will have gained all Light Magic spells), if the Hall of Trial is upgraded very late the hero will catch up in spells.