Class: Warlock<br>Specialization: Witch Queen<br><br><body_bright>At the start of combat, the hero casts Deep Freeze on a random ennemy creature for free.<br>Gains an additionnal level up every 5 levels.<br>At the start of each week, recruits in your Dungeon towns are transformed to Witches. Scouts are upgraded to Blood Witches (max is Level * 2) and Riders are upgraded to Shadow Witches (max is Level / 2).