Class: Engineer<br>Specialization: Fist Fighter<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each week additional Brawlers, Berzerkers or Battle Ragers will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.3*hero level. No extra creatures will join before level 2.<br><color_default>The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.