Class: Chieftain<br>Specialization: Centaur Commander<br><br><body_bright>Centaurs, Centaur Nomads and Centaur Marauders in hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defense for every two levels of the hero, starting on first level. Moreover they get +0.25% to their starting initiative for every level of the hero.<br>Additionally, a bonus amount of Centaurs is available for recruitment in your Stronghold towns each week (0.8*Level).