Class: Paladin<br>Specialization: Beloved of the People<br><br><body_bright>All Peasants, Conscripts and Militia in the hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defense for every two levels of the hero, starting on first level. Also, all Peasants in hero's army earn another +1 gold piece in kingdom treasury every day, in addition to their Tax Payer ability. Furthermore at the start of each week additional Peasants, Conscripts or Militia will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.55*hero level.<br><color_default>The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.
