Class: Runemage<br>Specialization: Golden Tongue<br><br><body_bright>Neutral creatures are more likely to join this hero. The hero has a +10% per level bonus to his Army Power evaluation for diplomatic calculations. Recruited creatures that are not Fortress units are transformed into their Fortress equivalent at the start of the day.<br>Moreover victories provide this hero with gold and resources.