Class: Witch<br>Specialization: Daughter of Darkness<br><br><body_bright>The hero starts with Dark Magic and Mother Earth grants the witch new dark magic and adventure spells spontaneously after levelups. Higher level spells can only be learned if the Hall of Trial/Walker's Hut is upgraded.<br><color_default>The ability to gain new spells follows randomly different patterns but is not based on chance (by lvl 30 you will have gained all Dark Magic spells), if the Hall of Trial is upgraded very late the hero will catch up in spells.