Class: Necromancer<br>Specialization: Spellwringer<br><br><body_bright>If an enemy hero casts any spell, it can be blocked in his or her spellbook making it impossible to cast that spell again in this combat. The probability of blocking increases with hero level.<br>Additionally, new Liches join the hero's army every day depending on his level (provided that some of these creatures are present).<br><color_default>Number(Level) : 1(5) 2(13) 3(21) 4(30) 5(38) 6(46)