Class: Witch<br>Specialization: Daughter of Thunder<br><br><body_bright>Lightning-based spells of this hero are irresistible for the enemies (except immunities and magic-proof).<br>At the start of combat, if there are at least 4 ennemy troops, cast Chain Lightning, otherwise cast a Lightning Bolt.<br>Furthermore, new Titans join hero's army at the start of each week depending on her level.<br><color_default>Number(Level) : 1(3) 2(8) 3(13) 4(18) ... 10(48)