Class: Warden<br>Specialization: Ringleader<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each week additional Druids, Elder Druids or High Druids will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.16*hero level. No extra creatures will join before level 4.<br><color_default>The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.