Class: Heretic<br>Specialization: Demagogue<br><br><body_bright>Neutral creatures are more likely to join this hero. The hero has a +5% per level bonus to his Army Power evaluation for diplomatic calculations. Moreover victories provide this hero with gold and resources.<br><color_default>The amount for each resource type gained after a victory is random between 0 and a maximum value; Max(Gold) = Cost*0.015, Max(Wood & Ore) = Cost*0.0001, Max(Precious) = Cost*0.00005, where Cost is the hiring cost (in gold) of the killed enemies.