Class: Seer<br>Specialization: Golem Crafter<br><br><body_bright>All Iron Golems, Steel Golems and Magnetic Golems in the hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defence for every two levels of the hero, starting on first level. Also at the start of each week more golems will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.22*hero level. No extra creatures will join before level 4<br><color_default>The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero. 