Class: Chieftain<br>Specialization: Cyclop Trainer<br><br><body_bright>At the start of combat, if Cyclops or Untamed Cyclops are present in hero's army, they gain 50 rage points per hero level. Otherwise if Bloodeyed Cyclops are present in the army, hero uses Fear my Roar on a random ennemy creature each turn of the Cyclops. If the first bonus is triggered, the other is disabled.<br>Starts with Absolute Rage.<br>Additionally, the weekly production of yclops is increased depending on the hero level. The bonus amount is 0.1 * Level.