Class: Runemage<br>Specialization: Lord of the Mountains<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each day, if an amount (30 - level/2) of Defenders, Shieldguards or Mountain Guards and 1 Rune Priest are present in hero's army, they are upgraded to a Thane, Flame Lord or Thunder Thane. Moreover, Flame Lords and Thunder Thanes cast their special Ability on a random ennemy creature at the start of combat.