Class: Gatekeeper<br>Specialization: Rusher<br><br><body_bright>Hero's movement points are increased by 5% + 1% every two levels. The cost of Teleport spell is reduced by half. The hero starts with Advanced Leadership, Quick Gating and Swiftness.<br>Additionally, new Nightmares join the hero's army every day depending on his level (provided that some of these creatures are present).<br><color_default>Number(Level) : 1(5) 2(13) 3(21) 4(30) ... 6(46)