Class: Knight<br>Specialization: Cavalry Commander<br><br><body_bright>Cavaliers, Paladins and Champions in hero's army get an additional jousting damage bonus equal to 10% + 1% per level. Hero's "Retaliation Strike" ability also does +5% more damage for every hero level. Furthermore every day, new Cavaliers will join the heroes army depending on the hero level (provided that some of these creatures are present).<br><color_default>Number(Level) : 1(10) 2(30) 3(50)