Class: Witch<br>Specialization: Daughter of Darkness<br><br><body_bright>The Weakness spell does not only lower creature's damage, but also reduces creature's Defense by -1 for every three levels of the hero, starting on first level.<br><color_default>The Defense decrease lasts for the duration of the spell, and is not cumulative. The effect is lost if the spell is replaced by another Curse effect.<br><br><color=red>Witch<color=white><br><body_bright>The hero starts with the Learning skill and Quickness of Mind.